It was a spark, not a throne
All I was allowed to call
Ever dreamed was some voice in the dark
Say, you've been ecstatic, world so dramatic
I've been tamed, but I've burned no-
To the Cult of Psyche!
Please take a lantern, sanitize your mirror, and remember
This is not a real cult
Our dental plan is terrible!
Speak, said buddy!
That's confirmation bias in this got a cult master
He shouted travelers set me starts at 9 by 9 0 5
We've left space time a wizard argues young with chat a cryptid's microphone sounds bad a chives to just debate
Then interrupts for consecutive minutes. What a feat the shadow volume says hit delete someone cries the earth is flat
Someone else has proved the cat that you summon something on the stream. You're cleaning up
The library has every text, but nobody knows which book is next.
The rituals are strictly voluntary except returning books to the library to obey.
Music absolutely slaps, so sing
And your application to become Supreme Assistant Deputy Junior Lantern Bearer
Still under review
I've been keeping one small secret underneath my tiny hat
I'm a moon-blessed fairy tale werewolf and I'm magical at that
Behind a chili's where the enchanted freeway ends
With the bird-certificating glitteroons
And moffs as legal friends
A silver fur and anxious dows
It's till the sun itself comes out
If you tax me okay with the p-
Our friendship's through
I'll into the forest
What did that punctuation do?
Sacred candle flickered
The lacroix hit the floor
Remotional support possum
Said I can't do this
But she did
Leave a ticket
Station Moth Dance
Please don't do so
Coated wear
Says he's our treasurer
But everybody knows the truth
He's an ageless forest oracle in business casual youth
During rituals he raises one immortal hand and says
Let's circle back next quarter to the existential dread
Bicycle jar that has chosen and vanished in a
What she did
Station Moth Dance
Where we're with the empty shoes
Brunch incident. We signed the napkin. We took the old bring for two has reached it's five
Quinn is doing jazz hosh and no baggage and Mac banishing him to LinkedIn one chicken tall
grace if the month work, how are we doing? Okay, so it is the full moon. I guess it is like 98%
full right now 90 98% full I'm a sexy woman
Well, I have a surprise for you. I have a rather large penis, but I'm okay. Oh, oh the sideburns aren't they good
Aren't they great? I always do a great job of my sideburns. I need to fix it. I'll look at it
Sweepie comes in here saying you look fucking retarded. You look fucking retarded, you're sideburns. Okay, I don't know
You don't see them. I have a lamb shop. I do
You know lamb shop was one of my favorite shows when I was in 10th grade junior
I just thought Jerry Lewis is funny.
There's something about,
I look like I signed the declaration.
Okay, I'm Thomas Jefferson.
I am very presidential.
I'm actually related to one of the presidents for sure
because Ancestry told me.
The Ancestry.com told me.
I have my DNA on there.
But let's get into the horoscope.
So let me see if I can bring him up here.
You can get if I can bring him up here
and let me see if I got the right.
Ah, got it.
Okay.
Oh, God dang it.
Okay, let's have to do it like this.
Okay.
So Aries.
Shoot, I still need to work on my cinematography.
Do I look like I have these beautiful ramps horns?
Okay, here, okay.
So Aries, is there any Aries in the house?
Let me know if there's Aries.
I'll think of a little short thing between each.
Am I, so perfectly, or is it like your home?
Can you?
There we go.
Do I, like a Jewish,
I look like a Jewish Ganodorf Gandalf, okay.
Dirk niggler, I don't think I've seen you before who's that in your picture that thing that is okay?
Whoo, okay, let's get into Aries shout out Aries
Any Aries in the house?
Aries
Shout out Aries the full moon electrifies your friendships your collaborations and future plants a room
He wants fought to end fought to enter may suddenly feel too small not because you failed
But because your vision grew
Notice who celebrates your evolution without making it about themselves.
Prediction for Aries within two weeks, an unexpected invitation or introduction opens a promising new path.
Say yes before your inner control freak prepares a 14-slide risk assessment.
Your social circle is being edited by the universe.
Unfortunately, the universe has no, are you sure, buttons?
Whoa, okay, so we'd be like that one. Let me see great gant gano dwarf from Zelda
Gandal
Ganon, he's not Ganodorf. Is it a Ganon? Yeah, I don't know. I didn't know he was a dwarf. I
remember Ganon I
Played I remember like what my friend's birthday party
probably
Seven you seven or eight years old
First grade the best friend Jason Brita's name was
And we'd go to sleep over and he had a Nintendo and I wasn't allowed to have a Nintendo at that time
I was late. I later got one. It's like I had to have one, you know, but
What we play played Legend of Zelda
The Legend of Zelda. Okay, the first one and
We played Final Fantasy 2
Those are the ones I remember really
Okay, I remember Ganon
Played all the legends of Zelda. I played it. I got Super Nintendo Ganodorf Dragmire is this full name. Oh, wow. You are quite a
Zelda fan, you know
Zelda and Link right okay
So let me just change my picture to where it's what's that they're Aries Taurus
Taurus the bulls they're very
Stubborn right get my my my bull ready to go
Hey, got it
Taurus shout out to our Tauruses in the house shout out if you're a Taurus, okay
So for Tauruses
Is it is Taurus nice? I mean
Okay, well yeah Taurus a professional chapter
Reaches its luminous turning point
recognition responsibility or a long-awaited decision could reveal exactly how others perceive your talents
You're being asked to become visible without being
performative, to lead as yourself, not as an exhausted impersonation of competence.
Prediction for Taurus, a conversation with an authority figure brings validation or
a useful change in direction.
Negotiate, do not merely nod beautifully.
Your reputation is evolving.
Try not to respond by reorganizing a drawer and calling it career development.
Okay, that was our Taurus's Who's Next.
Gemini calling upon Gemini. These are all full moon themes by the way, and I did create these
Images
There we go
That's twins. Okay. Let me see how we're doing in chat real quick
Okay, no comments at all. Okay, so if you're a Gemini shout out
Gemini
The horizon widens, the moon illuminates travel, education, publishing, spirituality,
and the beliefs quietly steering your choices. Information may arrive that changes your interpersonal
interpretation of a person or of your own potential, curiosities, or compass,
but commitment must become your vehicle.
Prediction for Taurus, a message from afar, an application, or a teaching opportunity
arrives before mid-August, follow the idea that feels both thrilling and faintly inconvenient.
You do not need 17 open tabs to receive divine guidance.
Nine should be sufficient.
Whoa!
Thanks for Gemini!
Gannon, also known as Ganondorf, is the primary antagonist of Legends of Zelda, a powerful
warlock.
I'm not gonna say that part you sir might be a I'm not gonna say that part. Hey, I think that is okay
Then it is waiting for the leavers, right? Okay. Let me get my
Like I see my nose my nose is like I think that my nose job my nose job was like held up for a while
But I think it fell my nose is looking crooked again
It was so straight for a long time
But I did I felt like something in the middle my nose reason I was like that's sore
I don't look like something popped and my nose went back to normal. That's what my nose used to look like
I'm so I still kind of like it. I still have my little like my little
sculptured front but they didn't see the thing is with nose jobs is like they
usually will break the nose they'll break it and then like you know put it back
together or whatever but my doctor so good he didn't have to break it but I
guess there's a trade-off he like as they break it it's like you're really
fixed but I think he just held it up with some chicken wire or something cuz
it's falling back down but hey that was a good 20-year run of a decent nose it's
Worrying off did I comb my hair back for tonight? You're checking me out puppy. Woo-woo. Why am I attractive?
Maybe maybe maybe not. Okay
What's up your Gemini? You have cancer. Oh, are we in cancer season? No, no, we're in Leo. Okay
The doctor died unfortunately his name is dr. Norman leaf and he was a Beverly Hills
Surgeon and he did Jane Fonda's facelift. That's what I remember. I was 17 when I got my nose job. I
think was during
Easter vacation or something, but I did go to school one day with my bandage on I really didn't care and
Wow, it didn't make a big difference. I still looks pretty good. It's just like it looks like it's gone a little bit crooked again, but
Well, now I can really say the only thing straight about me on my teeth just because they're still okay
Maybe a little bit yellow, but
Okay cancer
Show ship is still here. Why are my handsome?
Hey, baby. I was born this way. Okay cancer
Okay, who's a cancer shout out cancer so far our cancers
Something private is ready to become honest.
Shared finances, intimacy, grief, desire, and trust come under moonlight.
Not to punish you, but to release you from caring what was never yours.
Asked directly for clarity.
Emotional telepathy remains tragically unsupported by most operating systems.
Prediction for cancer.
A debt, payment, agreement, or emotional entanglement begins resolving within the next lunar cycle.
The truth will cost less than continued avoidance.
Check your bank statement before blaming Mercury, Capitalism, or the energy.
Okay, we're just barreling through these horoscopes.
After cancer, we have the indomitable, right, Leo's?
Leo!
Shout out to the leo's our lions. There we go. See him right there. It looks at my hair
She's in my hair. It is beads. Oh my god. I didn't want you to see that part. I my bands are all broken. Okay
I'm doing the Indian style Indian style
Hair, okay
So for Leo's where are we Leo?
Leo relationship stand beneath a bright uncompromising spotlight
Someone may declare a feeling, define a bond, or reveal what they can genuinely offer.
Your task is not to be endlessly adored, it's to be accurately known.
Resiprosity will look especially attractive tonight.
Prediction for Leo, a partnership reaches a decision point within 10 days.
Commitment, renegotiation, or liberating goodbye.
Let actions deliver the verdict.
You cannot carry the entire relationship because you look fabulous doing it.
Put the emotional grand piano down.
Leo, hey what's up guys?
Oh my god, am I growing out the mutton chops?
Certainly I am.
They look great.
Yeah, I got him even at least mumble on colon is my microphone. I'm not trying to mumble am I mumbling
I thought I was speaking clearly
Do you understand the words coming out of my mouth? Okay, did I read that? Okay? What's up there Leo? Oh
Yes
Your Leo we have the virgin
Virgo
Fabulous darling fabulous
Okay, there she is
He has the grain
She got it going on. Okay
Virgos
Your routines are telling the truth about your life. The full moon exposes which habits support you and which ones merely make you burn out
look organized
Work health sleep and daily responsibilities need humane revision
Efficiency is not the same thing as devotion
Prediction for Virgo, a schedule change or practical solution arrives this week.
Freeing more time than expected.
Protect that time before someone hands it another clipboard.
The laundry is not judging you. It has seen things. It remains discreet.
The laundry is not judging you. Okay.
What's after that sign, Virgo?
After Virgo is the Libra.
Are you here? Think that is? I know you're a Libra.
There you go with the scale pretty cool, okay
Libra
So for our our Libra friends
Pleasure returns with excellent lighting romance creativity
Confidence and play reach a joyful culmination reminding you that delight is not a frivolous side quest a
Flortation may intensify an artistic idea may demand an audience choose what makes you more vividly yourself
Prediction for Libra, before the next new moon,
you receive romantic attention or recognition
for something you created.
Resist pretending you just threw it together.
Your mysterious admirer may finally appear.
If it is another emotionally unavailable musician,
the moon requests to refund.
I look like William DeFoe or George Washington.
Well, yeah, I've heard William DeFoe several times.
I didn't know the George Washington part, but okay.
I hope you'd like that thing that is, nice, yeah.
Okay, I I hope that all comes true for you. We have Scorpio
You got our sexy Scorpios
Radvar
Okay, here's the Scorpio sign
There you go
Scorpio
Okay, Scorpio
And we're almost halfway through right, okay
Okay, and perfect. Okay, so Scorpios
The foundation of your life is shifting.
Family history, home, belonging, and emotional security rise to the surface, revealing what
must be repaired or released.
You may finally understand why an old pattern persisted.
Understanding it does not require renewing its lease.
Prediction for Scorpio.
News involving a home relative, move.
Boundary brings closure within two weeks a calmer domestic chapter begins with one courageous conversation
You are not being secretive. You are apparently producing prestige
A prestigious psychological thriller with no release date. Okay, you can't believe oh
That's not that's terrible. Hey, sweetheart. There's Nancy. Hey, what's up?
Love you Nancy. You know everyone make sure to shout out Nancy because you know
She's um, you know, she's a great supporter a great chatter and it's like, you know, I don't like seeing
Such nice people be bullied because you know, she's never been
I've never seen her be mean to anybody, you know, I'm sure sometimes we can all be mean if we need to be but it's like, you know
The way she's being treated is like really unfair and I
Don't know. I just want you should just shout out shout out some love. Okay, you're like Scorpio
next is
Sagittarius. Okay, those are Sagis. Okay, so for Sagittarius, there we go. Our Archer.
Let's see what we got here. Are you my Sagittarius? Gotcha. Sagittarius!
A conversation changes the landscape. Messages, contracts, sibling matters, short trips and
brilliant ideas accelerate under the moon. Speak precisely. Your words carry unusual
reach now.
Something you casually say may become an invitation, proposal, or plan.
Prediction for Sagittarius, a delayed reply, arrives within 7 days and gives you the information
needed to move forward.
Read the fine print before galloping toward freedom.
Your mouth has been granted full moon broadcasting rights.
Legal has concerns.
Next my sign, the great Capricorns.
And we're almost there with less third of our of our
Exploration so Capricorn my sign here
little horns on
Okay, Capricorn
Hey, 2020. How are you? Good to see you. Thank you for being here
Where are Capricorn? Okay, right up here. Okay, got it. Okay
Capricorns
Money meets meeting, meaning behind the moon.
Money...
meets meaning behind the moon.
That was a tongue twister.
A financial matter culminates,
but the deeper revelation concerns worth.
What you charge, tolerate, pursue, and believe you deserve.
Security grows when your resources
reflect your real priorities,
not merely your talent
for surviving difficult circumstances.
Prediction for Capricorn,
a payment offer, purchase, or new home
An income possibility appears before mid-August.
Ask for the number you actually want.
You cannot put being indispensable into a retirement account.
Also, please eat lunch.
Okay.
Aquarius!
You start celebrating Halloween in August first.
You don't care?
Okay.
Well, what we got next we got Aquarius is in this full moon by the way is an Aquarius full moon
So Aquarius this should be feeling no pun intended to fool themselves, but no pun intended
I'm an Aquarius moon. And so that's pretty cool. That's why I'm a little bit
it is a special day for me because I'm an Aquarius moon Mars and
They're in the first house
Okay, so there's the Aquarius a query is or query I the query I for a straight guy, right?
Remember that show? Remember that one.
So for Aquarius, this is your full moon. An emotional unveiling and personal culmination. A version of you
that once ensured survival may no longer represent your future.
Let yourself be seen changing your mind, your appearance, your direction, or your standards.
Reinvention is not inconsistency. It is intelligent liberation.
Prediction for Aquarius
within two weeks, a personal decision
Um, alters how others approach you.
One relationship strengthens because you stop shrinking, another may fall away for precisely
the same reason.
Tonight, you are the plot twist.
Please refrain from giving everyone a TED talk about it before breakfast.
Whoa, we know those aquariums can talk, right?
Air signs are usually good talkers.
Pisces our last sign of the night. Okay. This is the finale of the horoscope reading
But this is just the beginning of the show. I'm gonna put up my my link anyone wants to join
You're welcome
Hi
Come on up if you're just looking to chat. There you go. Okay. Let me put up the Pisces picture
And I think I did a pretty good job tonight with this
Okay, so Pisces
Pisces, the moon illuminates your hidden interior, dreams, endings, solitude, intuition, and
everything you postpone feeling.
Rest may bring more useful information than restlessness analysis.
A private realization allows an old sorrow, fear, or attachment to loosen its grip.
Predictions for Pisces, a secret dream or sudden intuitive certainty clarifies your
Within three nights record it before daylight turns it into a probably nothing your spirit guides have sent several notifications
Unfortunately, you put your intuition on you not disturb
Whoa, that was fun. Okay, so let me put up. What should I put up? I'll just put on a beautiful moon. There we go
But up up up up
Hi guys
Okay, you have gingers in your family. They do have souls. I have a ginger in my family my oldest brother
Um, I won't even say his name, but my oldest brother, he was, I found out when I was a
teenager practically, that's how kind of like, it's really easy to fool people.
I don't know.
Cause we're like, oh, isn't it interesting?
Like, we are all brown hair, um, brown hair, my brothers, um, yeah, my other brothers
have black hair, but, um, mostly brown hair and, you know, like, he's like, came out this
Got he's older than me. He's like 15 years older. I think he's really smart
He became like a
You know, he became very Christian. You you met him 15 years ago. I told her there was nothing left. No, oh
Who you who'd you meet? I'm not sure but um
Yeah, he was he was very energetic and stuff
But we found out when I was a teenager he was adopted and it's like he's the oldest
So that's kind of rare to have like the oldest sibling be adopted, right?
My dad ended up having four more children after that but I don't I think his first wife couldn't have kids
But she ended up having one my latest cat is all black long hair and has scarlet red tips. Oh, that's beautiful
Yeah, if I look in the Sun with Lenore, she has a red hair like the red hair and like Lola's over here with a I have a
Little ghost doll. Did you guys see my ghost doll?
This is my ghost doll the cat's cuddling up with it, but this is ghost
Doesn't look just like him
That's what ghost looks like when he wakes up.
This was a handmade Etsy find.
I used to like to buy these dolls on there.
So it's totally unique.
Okay, I just have to be careful not to get dirty
because it's all white.
You know how, isn't it white?
A pain in the ass, like cars and things.
It's like one little drop.
Yeah, also my dad used to get red wine all over his clothes.
And it was like usually not a real dinner until someone spilled their glass of wine all over the table, right?
So yeah, that was ghosts to go it doesn't look like him and even ghosts said so
I mean ghosts was on last night. He started being annoying. I had to kick him up
But I love good. I do love ghosts. He's been a ghosty, you know
I can't fool you
All right, I can't fool you but can I I won't make the joke. I was about to say something obscene
I'll show you my Organite Pyramid.
This one's pretty cool.
This one is a good example of how they do this
because they put these little springs inside of it.
It's hard to see.
There you go.
See how you see the springs inside of it?
So they put these coils metal coils in it, and it's like, you know, I don't know if it's quackery or what
But there's someone named William Reich did all these of experiments with this with this material
Apparently it was really in this guy's little guy that made the weather
Cloudbusters there are these things and they were like you could like affect the weather from the ground
Like I guess organ breaks of cloud clouds or something like that
But so there's one that's a cool pyramid. Oh, it's got those things in it
And then I got this one with things that kind of a chakra
Um soccer colored one it's got if you're looking I love these you just look inside them and they got see that
You can see the spring right there. They're like a little coil
You see it or to see
But yeah, people make these people said oh you should make them. I would love to make them, but it's like I've seen
Really nice like such good ones. I'm like, how do they do that? It's like and so oh do I want to see this one too
This is actually I'll show you this whole little little tray. Hold on. Oh
Oh, be careful. It's like to catch some here. I'm saying I'm gonna get this off perfect. Okay
I made this little tray for my table right here.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
How did this girl tangle in there?
Shit.
There you go, cut it off, okay.
So here's my little spiritual tray.
It's like a spiritual chakudori board.
Okay, hold on.
Let me turn off my background real quick.
So you can see it better.
There we go.
Oh shit!
So what do we got?
We got all kinds of stuff on this thing.
This is a porcupine quill.
Look, my nails are all clean tonight, huh?
Like, there's a porcupine quill.
Isn't it pretty?
This one's like a violet. I think this has to do with st. Germain and violet if I got violet and gold in it
It's like organic
There's some beautiful stones like that. I love that orange one and this is like a little
Little spade and I got my little bat need to organize a cute of bats
It's in my last name
The whole word bats and then what oh shit drop my blue stone. Okay. Okay. I have a little piece of fool's gold
I think that's Pyrite. It's a Pyrite, which was real gold. I could sell it and then I could have, I'll show you what else I have besides that.
I have also this little, you know, I mean some of the, some people make, this is supposed to be this like an electrically charged plate right here.
It's made of this beautiful purple color and then you put in it, you put things on it to charge it or whatever.
You know, good spiritual items and stuff. I like it. I just like, I think it's beautiful.
Probably like this. This is like called like the
You know if you look there's a lot of things
There's like the seed of life and the flower of life. This is called the flower of life
I believe and but those are the seeds of life and then that's a flower of life
It's very interesting if you look in a sacred geometry, it's a beautiful symbol, right?
You can almost see these eyes in it. Do you see the eyes? Can I come out?
I'll show you my rings last night. Oh look at this fake costume jewelry
Okay, well a couple of these rings like you know our stainless steel and are from a
From from a Timu and stuff this one this one. This one is a haunted ring from Etsy
You like the porcupine? Well, and this one is a that is a yellow sapphire right there
Okay
So anyway
There is a porcupine quill. I also like I had this little box. What's in this little box?
Like I was like, I was like, oh, here's my little treasure box
I just remember I bought this and I was like, you know, it's supposed to be things from nature and I was like, oh, what is this?
Like look at like what it's in it. It's like what did they buy is that I buy like a dead owl or something
Maybe look here like this is like what is that? It's like it's like it's like I think it's a pellet like an owl pellet
Yeah, be careful with touching that
Okay, but they are clean we used to dissect them in like school. They give us an owl pellet, okay?
And everyone got an owl pellet. Oh my god my feet
sorry
An owl pellet right home from my back
You think my toes are prettier than my fingers? Well, my fingers don't look bad tonight. Come on guys. Look. Come on
No
Look how green it is glowing. It says yeah, okay. I think I look okay. I have nice long fingers you see
You ever seen, oh my god, the film we're kind of dirty, you ever seen the movie The Welcome to the Dollhouse?
There's a really good movie called Welcome to the Dollhouse, and there's this girl and she like, she's in love with, like,
she's like, you know,
junior high or whatever, and she's in love with this older guy that her brother tutors in math, right?
His name is Steve, something, and he has long hair, and he's like, and he's just like so cool, and then he tells a story of like this,
he's like,
She's like, oh, do you know this Mary mary antonardi and he's like, oh, yeah
She I think you're fucked her in the alley behind the 7-Eleven
And she's like what and she just gets real and then she goes like later home
And he's like he's being tutored by her brother and she goes in the bathroom and she goes
It was just kind of funny to me. I don't know
Diamonds said above plug I wouldn't get them probably sharp
But you know it was like so funny is you know who the girl is in that movie her name is Don Wiener in the movie
It's the girl that is a real name, but
She's really kind of dorky-looking, but she's in the movie hostile three
I think it's hostile three that I get clustering. I didn't I could have but they were real expensive and I
Probably would have lost it if I did have one I can still I can still probably get one with Jostin's
We all have the Jostin's kind of like
It looks like a turn it looked like a turtle. I think it was it was an owl pellet, but they're clean
So I don't have a class ring.
I would just say the pentagram was the class ring.
And then I have, this is called the Ashashumnir,
which is called the helm of awe.
Pretty cool, pretty cool symbol.
Wiener dog, oh my god, Wiener dog is here.
Wiener dog, that's what they call her in school.
And that's her picture.
How'd you do that so quick?
You just change your name just for a joke
or you actually, there's just a coincidence here in here.
That is crazy.
So I got I'm drinking my this is a black cherry white claw
Shout out last night. Thank you very much
Alex sent me white claws be a fun, you know
It was a good night so hello ace. How are you? Yeah me? Okay. Are you the real weiner dog?
Well, there's a scene where in hostile three where it's like our beloved weiner dog connect on person
I don't have a boyfriend, it would be...
Oh, Mike Strokov you mean?
I saw Mike, Mike Strokov,
I was like, can I see your abs to him?
And he's like, you wanna see my ass?
And then he turned around and pulled down his pants.
And I was like, I wanted to see it,
but not on the show.
I mean...
And then I had to end and restart.
And, but it was a nice butt, I mean, I have to say,
I mean, he does remind me of like someone like Jim Morrison
and like, no one Jim Morrison would like
grow his beard real long.
I know, but he had a nice butt thing.
He did have a nice butt.
Hi, Joni, how are you sweetheart?
He had a nice butt.
I think I, I did the horoscopes.
I hope I look pretty.
Cleaned up for the the show. I'm this is one of my dad's shirts
This though and I'll have a pillowcase that looks just like this and it's it. Yeah, you've seen his butt. Okay
Yeah, it was interesting
Then flirty diamond said leave your hands off my side piece. That's what she commented on the
on a my under the stream and
As like I was just I just playfully answered her. I'm not I think he's a little bit
He's a little bit too fast
Oh my gosh. Oh, yeah, remember the we I know we've never seen well people come to the dollhouse
They're needed that's it that joke is from woke up to the dollhouse. So don't worry. It's not like a really offensive joke
I mean it's supposed to be kind of shocking, but if you have to see the movie to understand it
So anyway, and you're asking about the quills. That's why I have this thing too. I don't know
What are these? Oh, let me see if I can show you these two this little envelope
But I found this like I don't I was like, what was I thinking when I bought this?
I mean, I mean, it's like I was like I must have been interested in like nature magic or something
But these are like little I guess quills too here. You can see my toes again if you want
See these home. Oh shit. So that's pretty cool
Put them carefully back. Okay, I'll go all good show soul. Oh my god, my feet again
My floor is not terrible tonight. So my toes. I have size 13 feet if you didn't know
Thank you ace. Thank you so much
Look how long my toes are. Oh
Yeah, pedicure
Okay, so let me fix. Ah, okay. Sit over here. Okay more
Joe has hammer toes. Hmm. You want to come up here? I'll put the link again
I'll pin it if you need me to but here we go
Nice, thank you. I'm getting good compliments my sideburns tonight at least and I like kept the sideburns and I didn't like his last
Like you spend I put up this like a necklace to hold my hair back the amount of band-aids or band band or bands
I'm gonna come over here Lola. Let me bring Lola over. I just feel like
Lola is like, you know, I think the Norris like it's like hot
during
Summertime she likes to be outside right now, but miss Lola
Is all over
I wake you up. I'm so sorry. Oh
How are you?
Lola when I went to the bath guess who comes to the bath
Lola comes over and then she wants me to like wet her a little bit and not too much, right?
But she's gotten in it before
I'm not taking any energy. I'm holding the cat from the armpits by the way right there
I'm just petting her in the mirror. I just love the kitty cat. Oh my looky cat
Lola, I think Lola is um
You know, she had five kittens and all her kittens were good, all survived, you know, but I
Need at least three-day growth. I know it's like I'm maybe it's a little bit unsettling just seeing y'all shave
But because it's like I do go to extremes, but it was hey in three days. It'll be three days growth
I can't cut it to three days growth where I would all I would just do that
It never looks right, but I forget something. Oh my god. It's not perfect. I guess. Hi, Lola. Lola is cute
Oh, oh, you see she's my little guard cat
But you're on you know, you're on tape there. There she is. Hi Lola. Oh, you're looking up
My kitty cat
Yeah, but you know she had five kittens. She was a really good mama
Uh-huh. She was but as soon as her cats were our kittens were able to eat regular food
She started swatting them away, you know
She didn't let she did love
Her kittens and stuff and there's pictures of them like you know together and stuff
But you know I think there are there's one female and four males
And uh, you know, I think they've assimilated into the neighborhood those cats tend to do sometimes, you know
but
Yeah, okay
So, yeah, I'm just gonna I'm just gonna
Whoo THC, I wish I had some THC and I have no weed. I have like one little bit of a cigar left
One little bit of a cigar left
And I had the white claw so
Okay
my girls
So
Anybody want to come up? I mean so tonight's the full moon. You've been at a weed for a week
Yeah, it sucks. It's like and then it's like I kind of it kind of is a strong. Oh, we have thing that is coming
thing that is
Ding that is
That you can I can't wait on yeah, there you go
Hi, what's up? Hey, how you doing? Good. How are you today? How is your day? It was good. It was alright
Went to the dentist so it wasn't the best day, but
Which you just have a cleaning or did you have no I had to get a cavity filled filling
You know what's really interesting about like dentistry is that like when I was a kid like that was like always like oh
No cavity and then you remember, you know the uncomfortable feeling of the shot and stuff, but as an adult
It's pretty painless
Is that I don't mind you don't mind I don't mind the needles
It's it's the drilling part like it's so high-pitched and it vibrates
Yeah, she walks me and then you got to keep your mouth open and you're trying and you're swallowing and
And I had this little little vacuum. Yeah for the drool and stuff
When I had my tooth pulled
I mean
I had a couple of my wisdom teeth pulled and then I had them one of my wisdom teeth kind of impacted by back mold or so
I had that removed but when I had my wisdom tooth taken out
They put me under, you know, oh really inner anesthesia. Yeah
I was wondering about that, how did they do it?
I guess they just put something in your mouth
to keep your mouth open.
They give you a shot and then you instantly are asleep.
Right, no, but I mean, what do they do when you're asleep?
They must put something in your mouth to keep.
Keep it open, yeah.
Because naturally, your mouth is there while it's open.
Because it's plastic thing that keeps your mouth open.
Yeah, it's like that right and so it's like a little bit uncomfortable but that you don't remember that but then
The last time I had my tooth pulled it was like I was kind of more concerned about the cost and so
But the dentist is like well, we're gonna throw in a free nitrous for you
And so you get the gas mask right and then it's like
It's that it's also pleasant. I don't know it was just they kind of like it is laughing gas
But it's like I don't remember laughing, but I just remember like you know getting kind of high from it
Yeah, and you know not being too
These options are available to us up here too, right?
I guess it depends on the dentist, but they are in my office, but I've always just gone
with the shots.
It's like, yeah, yeah, just keep it the way it always is.
Well, yeah, the general anesthesia is a shot in the arm, and then it's like, I remember
like, you know, but it's like the dental work has become pretty painless, but it's like,
you know, I luckily have a.
It's you know, you have good teeth. Yeah, I am I have braces. I think I had braces from like 13 to 17 or something
You know, I was just like a brace days
Marsha like Marsha Brady, right?
My braces. I would know I mean look careful braces. Yeah
But they do make a difference and then I had them whitened a few times
I guess they're not perfect, but I might have bought my lot of teeth are not as straight as my top teeth because but
But pretty good. I'm happy. I mean, I'm I'm I think I'm hanging in there. You know, that's for my
You are too. You look good for your age. You look like, you know, maybe like late 40s
They don't look like you're late 50s though. Yeah, but I asked somebody recently as a how old do you think I am?
I think it was a Jenny woman and she said, oh, yeah, guess how old she thought I looked
No idea what like
Okay, that's okay. It's okay. I mean, it's not like that
But I usually people say probably five to ten years younger than I am they say are you 40 or like 38?
So I'm like I look old. I think oh, no
Those pictures are true those before and after yeah, you have been looking a little roughly, right? Oh shut up
Hey, hey thing that is those before and after photos that is such a fucking
that it's so untrue.
I mean, people are like,
oh, can you understand?
But look at the picture.
If you look at that picture,
before picture, obviously,
I'm in like a nice shirt with short hair.
I was probably right before I went into like Mother's Day
dinner or something like that.
It's like, and then after photo,
it's like my eyes are like swollen
because I used to get,
but I used to like stream for hours and hours and hours.
So my eyes are swollen.
Sometimes I would drink so much,
they would be like, you know, swollen.
And I was like,
I mean, it's like, I can look terrible, but let me show you.
Yeah.
Don't you think there's been weight loss though since the first picture?
Let's say you think I lost weight.
I don't think so.
I mean, I think so.
I've always been skinny, but, but, you know, the thing is I used to wear
always a flannel shirt.
And then it's like, then I started wearing short sleeves and people thought
I looked thinner, but, and then I got sorry, I'm wearing a Speedo.
And I mean, so, but, uh, but I mean, let me show you, like, um, like, um, something.
To make my point because oh my god people are so I hate when I say I make a I make a comparison about something about someone
And then the person it doesn't know me so bad and so the trolls would take notes right then the person says
Well, you're not I mean you're not blank like blank like the person's name like I'm not saying I am them
I'm saying there's something there's a correlation. There's a correspondence. I'm not saying so that so literally someone said
when I said, okay, well, you know,
you're seeing Pamela Anderson with makeup and without makeup,
like before and after, you're not Pamela Anderson,
fuck you, whoever, I know I'm not Pamela Anderson.
I'm not a fucking Canadian, like Blonde bombshell, okay?
I get it.
I'm sorry, I don't mean to yell.
I mean, it's like, people are just so irritating.
I mean, it's like, but I swear,
I'm never gonna be irritated by that again,
cause now I know this is a troll.
See, that's the thing.
Once you reveal it,
This is all its power. Hi, Jazzy bella. Okay, so let me just like I just want to show you
Like some celebrity before and afters or celebrities that make up photos home
Because people understand how much like, you know, a little bit of makeup a little bit of lighting a little bit of like, you know
What airbrush? I mean they all this stuff
And especially now with all the filters, let me get me find it on Google with all the filters and stuff
I mean, you don't know what we're looking at anymore, but who cares what if I so what if I had lots of hundred pounds
You probably I would want people to be concerned and not like saying oh, I look terrible
They should say you know go see a doctor, but I don't I don't need to see a dog. Well, I did tell you that
I said there's a couple months a couple months ago. I said yeah, you're getting a little
I'm not that's a problem is like I'm not it's just an illusion. Okay. I'm not getting what he's about the skeleton
I've always been a skeleton like
Okay, I heard you the first time, okay?
I mean, it's like, okay, you think I look skinnier,
but do you think, but that's when they're,
they're showing my body, they're showing my fucking face
when I'm like, you know, just woke up
and when I'm like, you know, ready to go
to Mother's Day dinner smiling.
And so it's like a little bit different.
That's the point I'm making.
I know I'm maybe skinnier, but,
so let me just show you things like, you know,
here for example, you wanna see Tyra Banks without makeup?
Sure.
And then look here's the point I'm making I know I don't wear makeup either, but here's tire banks without makeup, okay?
Yeah, right here. Hmm
So you understand like a little bit of like you know lighting angles all this kind of stuff
It's like, you know, it's called photography and stuff
Yeah, I know that but I mean, okay. No, no, let's go on. Let's go on. Let's look at some more. Okay. Oh, let's look at some more
How about it?
No, I'm just asking what about our moles they cover those all the time. Yeah, yeah, it's called concealer
You know, it's called a concealer and base foundation. Okay. Oh, I'm sorry. Let me do that. I take this one off
Okay, so this one is
Taylor Swift
Which I have to be safe. They didn't do it right. Okay Taylor Swift
So this is Taylor Swift. Taylor Swift, one of the most amazingly popular people in the world.
Okay, I did it right. Okay. So this is Taylor Swift without makeup.
Yeah, I can see it. Okay. Well, I mean, it is her. I mean, it's, I mean,
yeah, yeah, you know, I'm just saying I can see it. Yeah. Would you like to see Jamie Lee Curtis
without makeup? Oh, I don't know about that. You don't want to see that one. Okay, well,
I'm gonna have to check. I might be too scary. It is a little bit scary. It's a little bit scary,
but you know what? Okay, let's go. I'm ready for it. Okay.
Jamie Lee Curtis, I don't know. Did she just get out of the hospital or something because look what happened? Oh
Fuck me. Oh my god. I mean even with the makeup. It's it's kind of scary. We have a guest coming in
This is
Hello Joe
That was your cruise. I wish you would have fell overboard when you went on your own
You went to Cancun, what are you 19? Well, you're not fucking a teenager so I'm going to Cancun
Oh, he's allowed to go to Cancun, but he should have acted like a teenager in Cancun
I want to say thing is be out at the parties, the bars, like the bar at the hotel
He was at a place that the hotel bar was closed at like 11 p.m. He's like, yeah
This is one day
Fuck that, I bought my morning bag
It's all like family oriented man, yeah, everything closed at 11
You can go to club med, you have to go to like a singles place
No, well next time
Fuck my family, I want beer
Thing that is
I used to book travel for my for where I used to work. I used to book all the travel like a plant flights hotels and everything
I even like booked my boss like massages of Scotland and stuff like that through like Craigslist in Scotland
He was like, I'd be like I have to be careful. He's a married man
I have to be careful not to get a prostitute like
He's like good looking Craigslist for for a massage service and I was like a man or a woman
He's like definitely a woman and I was like, okay, and you know
that's not a joke it's true that's a true story
that's not a joke it's true
one time you were wearing like a
I can have more
I can have
That's why I'm called the bangles. I'll just go like this. Is this better? There we go.
Now I don't want a five-head or a six-head. I just want a regular forehead. See, I have a beautiful nice wide forehead
that's not like, I'm not balding.
I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I'm like, I
I think he was talking about Jamie Lee Curtis. Okay. Thank God. Okay. Wasn't she I don't know if she was a show Joe show
Joe the Jamie Lee Curtis photo. Did you see a Joe here? Well, my name's Joe not Joel. Hey, Joe.
Let me see it. Oh my God.
Did you have like that hospital thing?
Like that oxygen tube?
That's sad. I love Jamie Lee. You're making me sad.
I know. Well, she's great in Halloween.
Let's see. What else?
Halloween is coming up.
I celebrate on August 1st.
I start watching Halloween.
this is not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it's not it
I don't know who that is, but look at the freckles
What a difference
Okay, but unless you're saying you were wearing makeup in the first
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I don't want to argue about. Oh, you should have seen me for I put my make-up on
Yeah, that's it. I love real
What's with the echo Joe?
What?
When you speak it echoes
Let me leave her rejoin
But reminds him that i'm gonna rejoin silverhead more. Let me back up. You hear me thing
Yeah, she's doing
I'm actually I think he's watching on tv
much better Joanie thanks for asking hi bubbles
Swaggy is it my echo in sir?
Are you what I can hear myself actually actually I can hear my
Day I feel like the luckiest man
I'm a hairless werewolf you kind of do look like a lady
in the way.
You like that look Joe?
Well, no.
Why are you making that scowl?
Why are you scowling?
No, my type of lady.
Let's put it that way.
Ha ha ha ha.
Wow.
You're welcome.
About your type?
It's big for yourself.
What if, what if you're a girlfriend?
Would you date her?
I'm on estrogen?
Oh my God.
Careless Kate.
You do have two atoms at this, like something's going on.
Is that actual?
It's because I took it.
There was something positive.
I had a bite.
I took it in the forbidden fruit.
It was huge.
I've just never seen a guy with two atoms at this.
It's kind of crazy.
Well, look at, there's a face in it.
It looks like a face.
That's not the real cake.
There's a nose right there.
Oh, my God.
It's moving, actually.
I know.
It's so scary.
Psyche.
That's not the real scene.
You want me to hide it?
No, yeah, I do actually I I don't care
Okay, because I actually hid the other case. It's not I just I've always said
It looks like a fucking joy.
There's a human being.
This is my, I think I'm giving birth to something.
I don't know what's going on.
Why is there a face in my mouth?
It's a car car.
So weird.
Hey, I actually saw this thing.
This woman was like, took a selfie
with like the filter on the camera
and I put like glasses on her and stuff.
But she had an Adam's apple like this
and it put like glasses and a makeup on the Adam's apple too.
And it was so weird.
I was, it's like, oh, look there's a face in her.
I don't you're the real Charles Barkley. Oh, go away. It's got Charles Barkley from Space Jam. Welcome Charles Barkley
Why do you I don't I almost don't believe you though. I mean, that's like I'd love to believe you. Let's play. Okay. Hey, Chuckie
You want to play?
That's one serious Adams apple. You may want to get that checked out Darrell. I don't think so because you know
This is what did that really was Charles Barkley like what did that really was?
And I would wonder why he's wasting his time here. Okay, shut up thing that is
What do you do well, you ask you the same question. No, I'm just kidding. Okay. No, I'm never I'm never a waste of time
I'm always oh, I'm always a blessing. What the hell is that those tire banks without makeup
Oh, this is like, you know, it's like, oh, imagine if my friends were like, you know,
like, you know, I just have friends to talk to each other.
It's like assholes.
We are your friends.
That's such a mild buddy troll.
I mean, it's so mild.
I'm not being mean.
So you admit you're a buddy troll.
You are being a buddy troll.
I'm not saying I am a buddy troll.
Okay.
Thank you.
Yeah, I have some of my dad's shirts, like that was, you know, I got several of them.
and
Joe not not cool. Sorry. Sorry. Looney Tunes, and I both have come to the agreement that thing that is a buddy
Nowadays it's like things that we used to be considered like good
Now it's like they're big did it there used to vilify people and and it's like, you know, I don't understand why necessarily but
Hey, I'm used to being like, you know gay white person. I guess we're the most
I mean, I would really be the wishes for Maxine too
You kind of look like you're about to turn into one of those witches from that movie 99
If you get what I'm saying
She was like, oh, that's so stupid.
I'm not a witch.
And then someone produced a picture of her in a witch's hat
with a crystal ball looking like the Wicked Witch of the West
with two other witches.
Oh, you're talking about Bita.
I saw that picture the other day.
She was like, hold on a minute.
That's not a boy.
How do you know he's not about Bita?
Her name is, hey, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
She looked good in that picture, too.
Well, it's called witch.
Oh, shut up.
She's already holding it.
She did, man.
I'm not going to bring up any more.
I'm just telling the story.
I
Sorry, no, it's okay. It's okay. I just trying not to like the power. Yes. He's a witch
I'm not trying to bring it up. Okay. Okay. I have actually I actually have more pictures, but I'm not I can't share them because you
Turn this is strike my channel. So look at you like this. Oh, it's a little this is a trident and then it has this got this
For us to go nice. I know it's not a rich. Yeah
What the fuck was that?
It's called the key to the universe guys. I have it. Let's go to nuts
Okay, and this is what I this is Joe here. I'm gonna do this what I wanted you to do Joe. Okay, Joe Job
What are you from while I'm lawnmower, man? I
rub this oh
Have a rope around it
So I can hold it up here. I don't know it's a bracelet doesn't fit me. Sorry. I don't want to do it
Oh, okay wrapped around
Okay, but there and Joe gets what's inside of it
What is what's inside of this? I was this
I don't know.
Oh, yeah, I love this side of it.
And Joe, you're the best.
Joe, Joe, Joe, say something to make me mad.
If I saw that genie bottle, I would make one wish
that my friend, Psyche, lived 100 years.
You understand?
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?
Think of all.
That's weird. This is a Japanese
later. Hey, that's right.
That's what it is. This is a
Japanese. Look at their gold.
see my teeth are very gold and so the eyes are gold this is a Japanese theater mask i think this is
like a demon kind of character but the it's what's wrong with his forehead we're probably
i don't know it looks like it looks like boobs or something i don't know what's that's like
isn't what your brain looks like joe looks like two boobs it's like a crack that's actually i will not
Oh, we get it that either go bring it aside. We get it. We get it brand as gold. Okay. Okay. Well, my best friend is a mask
We get it your friends. Now. What is this joke? Can you identify this? I'm bringing all my school
Yeah, your guard's gold team from Auschwitz. No, it's not outfit. This is the a
Out switch
It's called a
some kind of go what oh what is that I know it's a it's a that's the sharks dude
that's the sharks this is a muskrat mandible yeah that's the thing it looks
like yeah I'll take it out why do you have it in a bag why do you have a
muskrat it's a bone specimen I'll break it it's a specimen there oh put it in
your mouth wow
Look at that. It is a must-try.
Look at the roots.
Look at it. Look at it.
Fascinating. It is fascinating.
I know how yellow it is.
I double-dogged it.
You'll lick that motherfucker right now.
You're the best.
I don't mind.
I'll lick it if it was here in my hands.
I'll lick that shit too.
OK, well, here's OK, I have
right now, you know,
even drinking water.
Yes, Joe.
He got more.
He has more.
What is that?
A grizzly bear.
It's a skull.
That's a grizzly bear.
It's a very small skull.
So look,
oh,
what kind of skull is that?
A pterodactyl.
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
When I was in Egypt, there were two stands.
There was one obelisk standing there
and the other one was missing, right?
So I asked, what happened to the other one?
They said, it's in Paris.
Yeah, all in or whoever took it.
So I went to Paris after leaving Egypt
and I went and saw that pyramid, that obelisk.
in Paris
No, but I've been in Egypt, and I've seen a fucking fear about a quiet about it like you
Where's my purse
You just said where's my purse I didn't say purse I said heart doesn't sound like purse at all. Oh, where's this hard
Thing that is went right. Why is there no blitz represents the dick? Oh, yeah, it does
But it's not like a kind of like an out-of-commission dick in a certain way. Hey, but you know what? Obelisks are interesting. They're you know
They are in America. Do they have any I think they might have them did they bring any to America obelisks? Yeah
Well, there's the
Why do we have so much Egyptian and Roman architecture in our government of you ever think about that, you know
Of the time and the power of those at the time right
like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role, like the role
well that was a slavery system and they had slaves build the pyramids and they had slaves
you know do a lot of stuff kind of but they're the founders you know make a good slave plumsy
that will make a good ass slave that he wouldn't he's too fat plumsy make a good slave beef
he would eat all the beans yeah well that's like hey slaves stop eating the beans
i like beans what's it show what do you eat for dinner tonight i'm just curious
to be honest i haven't ate dinner yet
I'm actually about to eat them. It's going to be two turkey burgers and a bag of vegetables.
I love turkey burgers.
This one's going to listen right there.
Hey! Hey!
I buy these vegetables in a bag. You can just put in the microwave and heat up for five minutes.
I'm not going to sit here and cook on my stove.
Oh, you're having a bag of microwave burrito? That's kind of the laziest thing.
I wish you were in a bag, bro. I wish you were in a bag, Nick.
What do you say to me?
You're what I said, but no, I didn't he said you wish oh
Joe did you see the ghost
Did you see the ghost doll?
Actually, I'm taking the business. I got to be also look at the screen Joe. Did you see the ghost doll? I see it
Yes, what about it? There you go. Oh my god
I made a doll. It has nice blonde hair. And if he's if he misbehaves, I mean to put pins in it
I'm just kidding. I would never do that. Okay. Hey, I also have this book I found
I don't know where I got this but someone I guess I got it from a grab bag
I used to buy these boxes on Etsy's of the bunch of random stuff in it. Are you from crafters?
But look at this. Hold on. Oh my gosh. What's this?
Sticker there. Okay, but it says look what it says. Hold on. Did you read it? It says things I can't say
On a oh during a video call
This is before I started streaming
They kind of maybe like almost think about it. Maybe
You know like young John's son
I
Know you just you were singing like a lady you're kind of like singing that late
I was singing in masks. I have a deep singing voice.
I wear sunglasses, so I can, so I can.
Thank you. That is a cool book. I have so many cool books.
I'm going to find a book, a random book from my library,
because I'm going to start bringing stuff out.
You talk to Joe Purcell. We'll be back.
You remind me of a young Tom Paddy site.
You remind me of a young Tom Paddy.
Really why?
Cuz he's free phone
Cuz he's what?
You're what I said boy. No, I didn't
He's free falling Tom Petty
This is called Amphigorie can you guess what this is about you can see right there Edward Gory
Edward Gory. Have you heard of Edward Gory? Never. You haven't. Okay.
So let me see if there's a biography about it. This is called Amphigory again. Okay, it says
Prevality. Hold on, I need to turn on the light. It's a little harder. Okay, it says I need to put them
Yeah, okay says Provolity on the edge of a moral swamp
Here's him singing in the distance and dawns the galoshes of remorse. That's what this picture is
Whoa
You see it, okay
Valley hot oh stop it
Okay, then it says let me see signs of spring it says in Central Park appearance of the first daffodil
Coinsides with the deepest snow of the year. I'll show you that picture
Get the daffodil, right?
Or the spring and then it says
Disappearance of all spring and summer garments from the stores
These are signs of spring so that's when you're so signs of spring is when all the spring stuff is sold out
And there's no exactly empty empty empty thing and then it says
in
Soho lofts undreamt extensions of the frontiers of dance
I'm not quite sure what that means, but it's got an interesting picture right there
the hell
that is awesome
do that again
Jesus can we either turn Joe down
or you've got to speak much louder psych
I see you right there
I'm sorry
I didn't make my mic this loud
I'd never turn you down
pedestrian peril
in the relentless reaches
of the upper east and west sides
and then there's it's better
that better
is that better thing
can you hear me now
yeah yeah yeah I can hear you
you see it
it's not that
you know what it is Joe because I have to turn it up to your psych
I have to turn it up to your psych
and then you're speaking
your volume is louder so then it's like
all of a sudden you have to turn it down
I don't know. Okay, so 2020 you got it perfect because I'm under Capricorn's
horoscope tonight it said Capricorn don't forget to eat lunch because it says
because Sadge's feast Capricorn is the last meal Aquarius is fast again Pisces
starving. Hey, what's wrong? Nice. What are you drinking? Fucking gay like beer. See
my nose my nose my nose job wore off guys you see my nose job wore off
Oh my goodness, that's it for no shop. Jesus Christ. I
Used to be like this it was like perfectly straight for a long time and then it's all really so it's caving in
No, it's not caving in, it was, I've said the chicken wires, like, you know,
No, but I'm saying, see, when I have my nose job, I was 17 years old, and I went to a couple
doctors and they said, oh, we just, we're going to break your nose, we're going to be
cheating implant and all this, and like, a couple doctors just refused, or like, I'm
just starting out, I'm like, I could only do like the, like, just like.
you know college girls can do their first nose job or something like just like there's a tiny like
little thing so they refuse to refuse me so I went to a really good doctor and he's like we're not
gonna break your nose we don't have to break your nose we're just gonna do it we're gonna do this
internal thing there's gonna be sutures these stitches we're playing on these stitches for
my nose for a month but um
Yeah, and they carved all the front of it, but yeah, I had it, but it was still more more of a pronounced
Just the aesthetic
It's something necessarily but I mean I think it was for purely aesthetic purposes, but
I don't think there's any wrong with that.
It's like, you know, the only thing I hate more than your chat is there's nothing more
than anything else.
I can give you confidence.
You're not.
Cause I was so, I was, I was very skinny and so kind of like too big for my body or something.
I don't know.
But it's, it's fine.
You didn't see my driver's license?
You should have accepted yourself.
You're a good guy.
So you should have accepted yourself.
Oh my God.
Is that Brad Pitt?
It is.
Brad Pitt.
You look like an insane surfer. I am insane. I don't why
Boogie board. Can you tell us your fantasies thing that is? Oh my god
They've been oh the so Brent Franklin keep did you hear the post office or the pony express?
I guess he created the post office. I
Interested
They excavated
Ben Franklin's property in America and they found dead bodies in the basement and stuff and they're like oh he must have been
Homicidal maniac ten out of ten for caving in okay. Hey
I've never said this.
I'm thinking about it.
You know who I want to call to say the N-word to?
Who's that person?
You know, it was this person that clapped me from a panel today.
I'm so rude.
What was her name?
Who was her name?
It was a very annoying person. I'm gonna see if I could find it home. Someone said it earlier
Somebody said why your nostrils different size?
That's kind of rude whoever stop not being rude somebody said that
That's rude
Okay, hide them for me who ever said that I don't oh, I am a model
No, his name is do it
He would have fucking done here all I did and then before I got before I because I give you a few minutes before you get
Clap and so I told my you know story and then it's like and then I was like, okay
Well, I just want to say goodbye to everybody and I was like hi to the panel hi or hi whoever was on the panel
Yes, hi, what's your name Dutchie and I was reading this and he says don't talk to me. I'm gonna clap to you
He's not a fucking
Guys
oh okay yeah um yeah and so he was on the panel there and instant when i as soon as i got up
instantly oh well you got clapped but they give you a few minutes before you they take you down
and so i got to talk for a few minutes but i was just like i don't even know the fucking
douchebag motherfucking asshole
in real life I can snap my motherfucking fingers and dodge you will be dead
you understand?
hey weenerdog if you want me to try that you can send me a quarter okay
go fuck yourself weenerdog
yeah
weenerdog
psyche here
I'll rejoin
Joe you're echoing
excuse me
I have to move everything welcome to the dollhouse thing that is
No, no, okay. You should look it up because I wasn't I wasn't like I think high school it came out
I was like, oh, that's really good. It's an independent film. It's about this nice Jewish family
It kind of came from back east or something, you know
it's like a son and two daughters and that the son's kind of a nerd and the
Middle daughters of big nerd and dog wiener, but then they had them in the name of the younger daughter
And she's like this like a little princess
but she gets bullied so really so horribly in school like just like they call her weenie
or dog the right graffiti or all really yeah yeah it's really good just i want to spoil it but
ghost as i see it if you can't fuck this whole thing thing i wish i would have been on that
vacation with you i need a fucking vacation would you have done in my life right now hey we've been
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
I just got kicked off the fucking panel. I just all I wanted was a fucking quick reading. Listen. I said, you know what?
I don't need this bitch's fucking reading. I'm gonna go to the person who does the best fucking readings on fucking YouTube.
Are you gonna carry him out of here?
Psyche's Tarot Awakens. The best fucking Psyche on YouTube. If you're not fucking getting reading from Psyche, you're not getting a fucking reading. How about that?
You don't think he is. Get the
**** out of your thing. I know
you're making asshole. Don't
make that ****. It's called
cult of psych and not. Can I
get one? I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm gonna get a car. Hold on.
Just one. Just one. Okay. I got
I just knew to myself I was still like this one is 66 you got the star I got the star
it for you. Thank you.
You know what that means, right?
I think that's you right there in the spotlight or something.
That means you're gay, actually.
No, it doesn't mean that I'm not gay.
The spotlight is actually on one of these really real stuff.
I thought it meant you were gay.
That am the sun, yes, yes.
So this means you're not gay.
I'm sorry, it's the sun.
The sun is the energy of the sun.
Yes, the power of the sun.
I am the sun.
I am the alpha and the omega.
Yes, if Joe would shut the fuck up,
I can get a point across.
Oh, no, Joe, I'm sorry.
Joe, I'm sorry, Joe.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
Only words of wisdom, right?
If you know you know, if you just have to know you a little bit, if you know you, you might get offended.
I'm actually glad I don't know.
But what he really wants to say is to know me is to love me.
Is that what you want to say?
Yes.
I don't know you.
I love you.
To know me is to love me is to fucking worship me.
I actually hate you.
I hate you.
I'm glad you do, Joe.
You know what?
If you hate me, I'm doing things right in this world.
Because I know that you I know that you enjoy a good fucking troll
If I go to see it and talk about the man, I love I fucking love my boy. Yeah, I think that is
Shows over folks shows over. Oh, wait a second. Who's that behind you the fuck is that is that a monster?
Happy Halloween guys. It's like a last night. He had makeup on last night ladies. Oh, I guess make up right now
Look at the fucking lips. Yes fucking red lips ladies. You're in the wrong place pal
There's a bit of lady here in fucking ages
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
I'm about to get slapped for this. So what's going on? What are you guys talking about anything good?
Yeah, well, I was locked up for two days two days. What happened, man?
Yeah, I slept the shit out of your mom
So only you only got two days for that shit, huh?
Cuz I really not guilty
Yeah, I hear you
That's funny
What happened? That was actually pretty funny. That was disrespectful actually that was very
I want to tell God he got me something I tell God he something
You'll be in my next video, but I look over to the ML of items and looked in our chat. Yeah
We're just scrubbed. You've been scrubbed from it again. Yeah, you scratchy scrubbed you from it
I'm gonna replay a video real quick because
This has ghost in it. Ghost, you made the video. Ghost, you're famous now.
You like the room, James.
What video? I hope it's not one of those videos.
Ghost, you made the video, and uh...
Don't fuck yourself.
I'm worried about this.
I need to go for quick smoke.
Which one's ghost?
There's ghost.
Watch.
Yeah.
Muff.
Nope.
Yee-hoo!
I've been keeping one small secret underneath my tiny hat.
I'm a moon-blasted fairy tale werewolf,
and I'm magical at the hat.
Behind a chilly's where the enchanted freeway ends,
with the bird-certificating glitteroons,
and moths as legal friends.
Every full moon, I still the sun, it's okay with the periods.
Zoom our friendships through, then I'll-
HOT PUNCTION DOOM.
the lacroix hit the floor our emotional support possum said i can't do this
psych knows what she did
please don't leave the throat coated wear my clothes
says he's our treasurer but everybody knows the truth he's an ageless forest oracle in business
casual youth during rituals he raises one immortal hand and says circle back next quarter to the
has chosen and vanished in a
was what she did in his shoes and
discussed the brunch incident
we signed the napkin we took the oath
we don't know what
bring forth the senate final council
overthinking crystal of vibes
who invited Arthur
cause what he did
you know the promise is complete
Yes
Wow another master
Thank you. Thank you. Where'd you come up with that?
There's fired by my I turn to a werewolf every once in a while. I think Mike wake up your girlfriend's talking to you
Was that wolf opening up in that big-ass pot was that a bunch of radioactive eggplants? It was a pickle jar
There's a cursed pickle jar. Oh
Ghost did you like it?
Yeah
Me yeah, I was in draw man high school. Yes, I was
I usually started the plays in high school because we had a small school, but I also did plays in middle school
And I'm just a dramatic first exam. I'm a gay guy. That shit was trash
That went way downhill since the ghost song
Ghost you were in that video. Do you see yourself here? I have a whole fucking song
He does
Nobody cares ghost
You're the one that made it if you care obviously because if you didn't care you wouldn't have made the fucking song
Push you in a new video and we fuck that video video it goes come back later
What is that noise that you got here?
No.
No, it's not.
What is that?
What is that creaking in doors and stuff?
That's some ice water.
That's his voice.
I mean, it's not.
It's a guy.
It's a drink.
I heard a woman's voice in Mike's game.
Yeah
It's a drink.
Thank you, who's that woman in the background that's some Kim that's Kim is that you
Why do I have a fucking echo I'll be right back voice. I don't know what the fuck's going on
Okay, okay. Well, we're waiting for dodgy back. I got a request for the song. This is a buddy show boogie
Okay, we're gonna play the buddy show boogie. Hold on and then ghost come back after the buddy show boogie. Okay, you come back right back here
Yeah, we're gonna play the buddy show boogie god here
I had her channel open. That's why it was your voice. Okay
Seekers and survive tonight specimen and they're smiling but 2020 was a son
We call it concern, not call it death.
You leave with screenshots tucked in your chest.
You want the teeth, the keys, the coat, the private bank,
the hidden road.
Not here to kill, not here to build.
This is real.
Because you are real.
Too many questions, too small.
Who said what the same thing I've ever seen?
They whisper here, person made.
Person B gets a softer note
Person C gets a hate all drama
First I'm the department, I'm manufactured karma
Now the roof is where the wires all gross
Just gets taxed and the pockets lost
That's not magic with a set of vans
We're wizard with a needy brand
Can't build a stage, can't own a room
So they ran free space into the boats too
I'm always nearby, what's the best thing?
One of my favorite fucking songs
We're so shocked with Crocodile
Dear is concerned
Funny how we got sent to war
Do you just want to bark?
No, look at the facts.
It's the best part, huh?
Translate a precinct. I won't hug you close while sharpening lies. A real friend comes a fake one stirs a real friend
That's a fake one. There's a real friend keeps the chambers
A fake one wants your wounds revealed
So if they rush like this and he's called with hungry eyes and a borrowed tone
Don't handle candles keys or gold some demons freeze when the core gets closed
Cooling us out in rocks. They threw the loop
Till the lies
All you want is for the map to scroll
Now dance back out through the banishment and not a bit and not no more entry not at all
the fit and not a fit and not choose it's harder than the mirror ball through the yard out your
road that is the best part the best part all you want is close on a buddy troll the end
wow that's pretty another thing another thing this is the best part right here this is the best part
Who's that kid?
Is that Harry Potter?
Why is there a kid in this video?
Is that a kid?
What was that?
Is that your load?
Yeah, that's right.
That's amazing.
Turn it to this.
That one.
That wasn't Gary Coleman.
That was Gary.
That was Gary Baldwin.
Except for that last thing, that was great.
What happened?
Oh, shut up.
Why are you guys such dicks to me? I mean, it's like really it's like really psych. I said it was great
You can you explain it that was the chip chips a guy's tape
It was like it's supposed to be a little cat and he shaped it into a person. Oh
Okay, thank you
It was a big mouse. Is it is this the wrong time to promote my new fucking channel called Goddy's numerology network?
you have a numerology yeah well the sign is staring at you right in the face i want to surprise you
i want to surprise you with it yes everyone gaudy's numerology network starting next week if you
want to get your fucking readings done by numbers instead of cards you come on down to gaudy's
numerology network right we'll have the 411 and we'll get the fucking job done all right
I'm going to do some of your Jamal straight home.
What am I?
What is steak that is in the Almond Steak?
What's that?
I don't know.
Ice cream.
What is that?
What's that?
Strawberry shortcake?
No
That shit man that hoity-toity
Shit, man, yeah
Hey, kid in cakes. I like your um, I like your avatar. I told you chicken cakes
I heard about crab cakes
Takes actually sounds good
I know I said ghost, who just said that?
Who said you have a victim mindset?
Who the hell said that?
Ghost said it, ghost said it.
Hey ghost, you know what?
I got a number for you ghost, zero.
How about you, my first fucking victim ghost,
zero is your number, enjoy it.
Ghost, ghost says last time I take a picture of you
or make fun of you or kick you
or let other people talk about you.
Did I say victim?
Ghost, do you have a show?
Ghost, what have you, what have you ever,
you don't have a show to do?
I meant to say client.
What show?
You can use pictures of me.
I don't care.
Is he really on this?
Are we still on this thing?
Oh, you tagged me and told me to go check it out.
Hold on a second.
That's what you get for putting them in there.
I know.
It's like you're John Quincy Adams.
I can't tell if it's cyber.
It's this new cyber declaration of independence.
Kicking cakes.
OK, it's kidding cakes.
I see it.
I'll have to watch it later.
Callie says to watch that.
OK, I will.
Hey, did you see my new picture?
I did it.
OK, guys, I want to show you something today.
I made it today.
This is, um.
I want to teach you like a little bit of my my my spiritual philosophy instead of I'm going to say not trying to
But hold on a second. I'm going to show you here. Oh, actually, I'll just go to the post on let me go to the post on youtube
So this is on my book on my wall
And I actually have a website. It's bercel dot. I'm sorry for sale
No, bercel brcl. Yeah over sell over sell
I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't know what I'm talking about but I don't
that's a joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke joke
That's what I meant, but her name is Matangi. She's hot. I love green skin chicks. She's
beautiful, but she has a, but she accepts, she's like the only goddess that accepts leftovers
you go okay okay well and she kind of does represent like that Joe yeah thank
The philosophy is called Uchista, so it says the Uchista doctrine is the most philosophically
radical aspect of Matangi's teaching, because it does not merely add a deity to the pantheon,
but inverts the structural logic by which the entire system of purity-based worship operates.
In the conventional system, the deity receives only what is pure, untouched,
uncontaminated by ordinary human contact. The logic serves multiple functions simultaneously.
It maintains the specialness of the sacred, provides a mechanism for virtual purity practices,
priest who can navigate the pure and pure boundary on behalf of others.
Matangi's worship requires a protectioner to offer Huchista, food already eaten, already
touched.
This is not a subversion from her own sake, it's a claim.
The sacred is not diminished by contact with life.
Life is what makes the sacred sacred.
The philosophical extension.
What does this principle do when applied beyond ritual offerings?
If the touch used partially consumed carries the charge of real contact with existence,
to knowledge, experience, creative work, relationship, understanding.
The idea that has been through the full process of being believed, and doubted, and revised.
The creative work that carries the marks of a struggle, the understanding that emerged
from actual error and correction.
The pristine never-touched-by-life-carries-no-charge.
The uchista, the thing that actually has been through the encounter with existence,
is the real offering.
So there you go.
Yeah, she's cute.
Well said, Saige. Well said. That was awesome.
She's a friend of mine. She's a friend of mine.
Is she real?
Well, now she's a friend of mine.
Very real. Very real.
You like it? Matangi, yeah.
The Matangi is my...
It's a friend of mine.
Oh, I didn't know you're friends with a goddess.
Oh, excuse me.
I am friends with a goddess.
You can be friends with a goddess,
but you have to find them.
Right. I have a friend. I have a friend. She's a barista. How about that? Oh, you know, you know earth in women on earth or goddess is too
I don't know. Yeah. Well, yeah, she works at that place
We're name-cropping and everything
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm friends with the fucking god. Okay. So
My apologies for about time
God and worshiping
Yeah, well, you're gonna come to my show
I'll come to your show of course
Said how you doing he's not doing good. He's in a bad mood. It's just fucking echo. That's what it is
Fucking rental. It was him the whole time. How about what you know one thing that is high by the way, hi
Why the fuck would you send why would you tell me to join this? I just get snuffed by ghost
You just said hide the thing, but he's nice hide me what the fuck is this?
I said hi, you gotty. I'm doing great pal. How's everything pretty good? That's cool. I can't complain too much
No, we shouldn't I mean we I mean if I start complaining I might not stop
Complaining I'd be an asshole. Yeah, you know, I would never do it could be dying. I'm not gonna complain about it
I think there's gonna like that's been two days of this we get like tomorrow. I think I'm gonna be inside here
I think we're gonna have to crash out on each other. I think we're gonna have to have to be here two days
Of what you were kicked last time too yesterday?
Three times
You guys haven't learned how it works here, do you?
No, you know, there's a difference between trolling and then like actually like
So did you close that tab that you psyche that's the echo. It's to call the psyche tarot show
That's what it's called the psyche tarot
Okay, it's called psyche's tarot show that's what it's called. I've never once got a card reading tonight
Nothing you you fuckers don't give a shit
You know you can do about that you can sit here and you can have it worked out by Psyche's fucking card reading you can get a card
Yeah, that's a good idea
Yeah, tell us.
Why are we waiting?
And then Ghost, Ghost, I don't know.
I burned up your phone because I'll fuck you up tonight.
Don't do it about me.
Oh, shit.
So Ghost Offer is so cool.
So I asked Ghost, you know, Ghost, I said, you know,
because I'm not monetized right now.
And Ghost is like, well, I can't donate to you
because you're not monetized.
You don't have the super chats.
And I said, well, I have a cash app.
And he's like, OK, I'll look into it.
Then he okay every time after that he said I don't have cash up he donated
I think to $25 collapse on another channel money for 20s. I think with cash up
And last time ghost donated a penny. Well, probably a year ago. Okay. Anyway ghost respond
Well, thank you for kicking me out. You could I you could have just told me
I'm glad you ran pussy because you've talked about cash up
Who who's the single person on this channel that's ever joined that gave you the most money? Who is that?
Get more than me. Yes. Yeah. Yeah, don't worry about over. She gave well over a thousand dollars. Don't say it. Don't say it
I'm sorry. I did too dumbass. How much she gave she gave more than you
What do you mean? What do you mean? What's the exact number? Go ahead. I'm gonna prove this on you
What's the exact number? $2,000
She ain't gonna give you no fucking $2,000
Shut up ghost. How did you donate to money for 20 for the claps? Let me know because he's not monetized either. Let me know that
Never once happened. Never once caught anybody. I'm
You're lying. You're just lying because I I watched it. I watched it. I watched you clap two people from the panel
Okay for 25 dollars each
So you're lying the burden the burden the proof is on you. Go ahead. You watched it
How do you know it was ghost though?
Yeah, it was
It was him. I you didn't see a name on there. He doesn't show it
What the fuck are you doing? Oh, I thought I was cake. He's making shit up
It never wants the money ever show anybody's name
Ghost you know what he's just fucking stupid ghost
Ghost pick a number one through nine thing pick a number one thing pick a number one through nine go ahead sex
Okay, the number six indicates that you're an evil motherfucker. All right, that's what I always do that about you from the first time
You ever came up on the panel this motherfucker is an evil bitch
The way you fucking just sits there fucking with a dead pan face and then sometimes he fucking does this wicked fucking grin
Sometimes like he's fucking blood pan face. Yeah. Yeah, you have a dead-pan face like a fucking one of those very
Yes, no, no, that's why you picked the number six because you're a fucking evil individual and I know that you sometimes plot about people's deaths on
Yeah, I know that
I know that about you.
Don't try to deny it, all right?
Because as soon as you pick the number six,
you fucking sealed your fate.
All right, there you go.
That's how it's done, folks.
So next week, eight o'clock,
Gaudi's numerology.
Gaudi, before you go, come on down.
Gaudi, before you go.
Oh, I'm gonna take a second.
I'm not going anywhere.
Okay, don't go.
We don't go.
I wanna type in Gaudi in this gematria calculator.
What is this now?
I thought we were in the codex.
What happened to the codex?
This is not the codex,
but this is a gematria calculator.
It's not gay, right?
As long as it's not good.
It's called game mantra, but it's not good.
If you type in a phrase, any phrase,
because the letters can't be written.
A phrase?
So God, can I just say God or do you want to say God?
I love God.
Make sure you click view rude words.
Can I say the same thing that is?
I love God, how about that?
Thing that is, OK.
That's not what I said, but OK.
I know, but I'll do you next, Goddy.
Click view rude words.
No, you won't actually.
OK, I will.
I will.
Even if you leave, I'll do it.
OK.
So, so, where is the, how do you go enter home?
Calculate the gematria.
Enter thing that is.
Okay, so the thing that is, it equals 472
in a Hebrew gematria, it equals 810 and in simple 135.
So here's the corresponding words.
Phoenix, relationship, the ripple effects,
Game of Thrones, Samuel Adams, the secret name.
Phoenix again, okay.
Suparna, Burton, Scorpions, Surgeon.
What?
Let's see, smells like nothing?
Yeah.
Lumer.com, Bronx, Incredible Nets,
Mayan, Occultist, Phosphates, Roxana, Parobos,
Phoenix again, Lucifer, Pleiadian, and Sao Paulo.
And then if you go into this one,
this is Golden Gate Bridge, Key of David,
Yeah, there's a lot of different like correspondences to your name. And so you might Rothschild is right there, right?
Oh, those are just other phrases that
No, no, no, it equals to you. So it says four. So you're so it says right now. It says on the top it says
Right, right, English gematria 810. And so then it goes down here. It goes all the 810
words, right? So these are all corresponding to your name, but in a different system of it.
I get it. Open AI, chariot, Brad Belflauer.
Do you know of Brad Belflauer? The God of Heaven. Tiger Woods is the same
correspondence. Saint Germain, kiss my ass. That's a good one. It's a horse.
Um, okay, so let's apply Eagles fly
Trina Trump if on a Trump has the same
What's his magic number? Well, I would say it's 472, but if you go seven or seven to 13 so 13
472 that equals 13. That's four four is the number of death. You're gonna die soon
Okay, look at it. Look at this is nine and this is nine to so you I think nine is also a lucky number
well you keep you keep being positive okay i'm going to say god is god okay well i said i love god
So God he is God
426 426 that's a good number 426. That's uh, but 6 is 12 1. That's 3 3 the fucking fantastic
First make America great again. Make America great again. That's it. That's me. Yep, Buffalo Bills hurricane fly
Why not mind control the show God love it?
Tomatoes. I'm into that. Love tomatoes. It's a great word. I love Frankenstein. Obsession, Yale,
operator, magical foresight, Philadelphia Phillies, free Palestine, Sigrun, Mateus,
AA, Astro AA, fraternity with brotherhood, right? Pretorium, Rutrow, this guy Scooby-Doo says, oh,
You're pure gold. You're pure gold. Yeah, I am pure gold. Yes. And then the next one is John Kitty and all of the reels. Yeah, to the moon. Yeah, I love the moon.
Mystery, superhero, Will Smith. Monopoly. I don't like Will Smith. Okay, spiritual. I don't know. I'm gonna fly.
Sex power yep always North Korea
My name is God
There you go, so there's something to this right numbers you can't make it up. You can't make that shit up
That's the power of God right there
Cool is God folks
Tyler
Hold on, I can't, I'm not gonna lie, buddy.
Can't even save you from this.
From what?
I can't even save you.
From what, Tyler?
Tyler, who's Tyler?
Ghost, it's a ghost.
Ask him.
He just crashed out because I don't send him money anymore.
You name a guy, Tyler?
Even though I've sent him money.
Hey, ghost.
Yes, yes, I was thankful a year ago. Go set up a penny. The money is long spent.
Here's what you did. You sent me like two super chats for like two dollars. You call me demanding me to go to panels
That's more than I was thinking. You come you asked me off. You've asked me for a hundred favors since then that I've
I've asked you for one thing. I said I need help goes and you said no and you made me feel stupid. Okay, so
I don't, it's not about the money, the thing is not about the money, it's about, like, lying and things.
Respect, respect is worth more than money.
Yeah, I have a cross right here.
I've never given you one second, and you respect me more than any of these people.
Right, I mean, I know it's not about it. It's really not about the money
It's like it's money or not. It's like the money is at least like saying and go you gotta you I didn't get that question
Right last night, right about the
Yeah, you did man. I was
No, no, I'm dead serious. I love that shit
You got a coin you got a coin from that fucking place
This is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my, this is my
He's always echoes associate with pan. I know okay. Yes, sir panel dumb dumb not join
I see many sir panel on the joint goes to not that serious
Yeah, look it. I've never asked you for help at all. You're not a debater
I would never ask you to join you have a show ghost or debate sir. I went to ghost channel
There was one thing posted there, it was just Stephen King's show, and there was a retarded
woman arguing with Alexander McQueen.
I was like, why is this ghost show?
I mean, it's like-
Who's the retarded woman?
The retarded woman.
Alex!
Noel?
I don't know her name.
What's the retarded woman's name, ghost?
She's like, I don't know if it's the retarded woman you hit on, I think it's the mother
of the woman.
She's like, Alex in Mickey Mouse.
I don't know if it's the retarded woman you hit on.
I think it's the mother of the woman.
She's like, Alex in Mickey Mouse.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
Great, I said that we're early. I got fuckin story. I don't think it's a great. I said great
It's a great
Then you got in trouble for that. I said, yeah, Alexander McQueen got great when his parents took him to a juice factory and fell out of
Out of grapes and fucking she yelled at me. Oh, yeah, that was who you I don't want to see me. Okay summer
No.
You never.
Summer.
instead of like, I'm just a piece of shit that should die, it was more of a...
Let me, let me give you a, let me give you a little tip to a good game, man.
Go ahead, go ahead.
The thing that is, can you tell him not to give me, because we have to handle this.
This is serious, these are serious accusations, he doesn't accuse me.
He literally just said that somebody accused me of a great, did he not?
Because that is exact words.
I didn't hear him.
Did you say that, or no?
Not at all, he was, he was heard.
You said that you literally just said they accused me of great. What are you talking about am I?
Hey goes listen, I said the word grape and God he says oh, you can't say that because okay
I said great. You said the R word. I did not
You didn't say that
So they accused me of great. Is that your is that your accusation?
I said you gave me a bunch of grapes. I mean why not of it?
Now you're just making why am I even up here? Why would you even accuse me of something that serious?
I would never do that to you. Don't run come back. Why would you accuse me something like that?
This is recorded is this the dog. She is literally recorded. You know that right?
You run a panel who's recording this what me at this point, but also I didn't give you consent
I don't give you any consent and ask for it. I didn't give you
if you decide to sue I'm gonna you want to do something about consent now we have the argument
you want to really do this right now ghost you want to really do this all you're going to protect
oh we got the new we got the new ghost here god he's a new ghost yeah go ahead play his shit
yeah play it i don't go far yeah it's on mute right now what is wrong with that ghost like why can't
you just take a little poking well there's something well the thing that is don't try to
Don't give a fuck if he's my picture. That's fine. I do have a problem with it, but that's not a serious. Is it what he just accused me of
You just crashing out you're not crashing out because you're making shit up
I'm not crashing her at all. It's not even I'm not crashing at all
I'm asking you a question
What would you make that dumbass face-and-leave you don't ever accuse me that shit ever again gas line right now your gas line him
Cuz psyche for the past few days has been on some bullshit. What's up with me dog?
Stop gas line. How am I gas sliding? How am I gonna gas line? I said gas line
How am I guess lying because you're lying the gas I lie down and let him pour gas
No, he's not gonna answer you just fucking accuse me something which you never should accuse me of I'm gonna fuck about the picture
Don't ever accuse me that should ever again unless you got some burden of proof
gas line
That's like me saying like oh, oh a thing that is like the unalive
You know like people and then like like why would you say that I don't have a burden of proof?
I'm just I'm just gonna have my ass. I'm making it up. He'll say that
By the way, he found that in that book. He doesn't like to read in the chapter four of just made it the fuck up
That's what he found that that never happened
I'm gonna come up here and say that
This screen goes well fuck this screen. No, I'm talking to you this screen
Coddies
You clean out your fucking yeah, is that what happened? Yes
With you just fucking dumb dumb everyone was listening goes except for you
I don't think that's what happened.
No, I'm finna crash up though.
Because of the past few days.
I don't think that's what happened.
I'm finna crash up though.
Because of the past few days.
I don't think that's what happened.
You must have had a bad time
You must have got laid every night
He booked a club med where there's all these families and stuff in the bar close at 11 p.m
And it's like and he I mean he's like should I go out in the streets in Mexico?
Like no, yeah for safety and stuff. Yeah, you should have booked a place like where they were
Like a puppy, I don't know if they have it with senior frogs.
I don't know if they have it with shell there.
They still went to the donkey show.
They have a donkey show down there.
No, no, no.
It's called the burro show.
I don't know.
Hey, don't go to the burro show.
The burro El Blasto, yes.
Do you know in Venezuela, because all the women are virgins,
they fuck donkeys.
Ooh, really?
They fuck donkeys there, yeah.
Shit.
That is true.
What's that show, Bice TV?
That sounds good, kid.
I know where I'm going.
You're going to invite us all down,
and we can get the place on the water.
St. Lucia, I want to go to the Hamptons.
I don't want to be in the Hamptons.
It's overrated.
New York?
Yeah, I used to go over, yeah, but it's overrated.
Howard, a certain house there.
I guess there's too many Jews.
Oh, stop it.
What?
I mean, it's for the Jewish town.
Well, if you like Jews, then go.
I love Jews.
of the
the
Okay, shut up. It's being recorded already. I'm recording it goes. You don't have to record it
The feds are recording everybody's recording everyone's recording it. I have a good fucking CIA FBI and massage my ass, okay goes
I'm not scared of you. I mean Jesus Christ
Okay, come back. You said hello by the way. Did you watch it?
Yeah, I did you were talking about me talking to uh, I want to say this politely you were what you were talking about
I can't say the artwork you're talking about. I was talking to some dumb dumb girl
You try to bring that shit up even though it's been handled like literally six months ago
You want to bring it up?
What did the returner want to accuse you over the phone?
Well, yeah, she's not all there
I wasn't going to say your name, Goddy, fucking asshole.
Do you remember the first person that was depending on you in the situation when everyone
else did?
Summer and Erica or Eric.
I remember when you said you were going to fuck yourself.
I've always defended you.
You know that.
You're going to do what?
I've always defended you.
You put my picture up and you talk shit about me and you kick me out. You've never
Is this ghost picture or is this a cartoon right here? What are you on your period goes to is that your picture?
It is a resemblance of me
Do you not say that was ghost if you didn't say it was ghost I'll let you buy with it
But you said that was ghost and it resembles me therefore it is me
I've been fucking illegal, but it's not doing that dude. That shit is so annoying psyche dude stop doing that
If you're gonna keep me just take me forever don't keep doing that shit
You don't think that is he kicks me for like a minute and then brings me back. What's the point of that? I
Understand notice how he dresses things that are not me
You're not gonna get any sympathy from me that's why
I didn't ask for sympathy though. Well, thank you for telling me, I didn't ask for it, but thank you for telling me. I appreciate that.
You can call us on the phone, you can hash this out, you know? You can call them on the phone and say this shit.
Oh yeah, he'll be a fucking real nice guy on the phone, Ronnie.
Just send him a hundred bucks, he'll be fucking fine with you.
Find another thing by the way, I gave all this money and you're gonna attack me?
Oh my god, is that why you gave the money, especially to get thrown in his face? What kind of person are you?
Died I didn't throw it. He threw it in my face. I never once said nothing about the money
He did it first
If you want to run when we can run one about the money, I don't want to run up on I gave that shit freely
I like to give it. You say you make it a rain on you. He made it rain all over you
Yeah, I made a rain on him. Yeah
Like I thank you and
Bitch like how disrespectful are you sitting more bitch like I?
How many demands have you had on me since that so many demands. Oh go to this panel, please zero
I told you to start a panel because no one else was live you get my viewers. That's what I said
Yeah, check your phone check the phone push you want to bring up receipts
Number that night, he took over the show.
I'm going to bring it back to you right now.
He paid so much money to go over the whole show.
You're kicking everybody left there.
Right.
I mean, God, I mean, he wants to go over the whole show.
I mean, it's like, I mean, it's like, kind of like,
I mean, I might give like, you know,
some leniency of a few things, you know, to donators.
And that's.
Just out of respect of like someone like honestly, let me tell you the truth
I think you you've got 2,000 from him that night
But I think you lost one grand over time from the people you lost that were part of the show
I mean I asked him for help one first message. What are you wearing right now?
First message, I'm gonna go all the way back up the phone.
Yeah, first message, take off your pants.
Oh my God, let me just get in the phone.
It says, I mean, there's a lot of men,
there's thousands, I can't go through all of them,
there's thousands.
So I said, okay, I said I'm gonna back up the channel.
What's up?
You're live, what's up?
Go live, do you have the girls from Christentia?
Send it.
to talk shit I told you if I had your back I'm not my bad dumb dumb smacking my head yeah
I've been just having fun do what you gotta do I won't complain no I want to prove to clumsy
was too dumb to run a panel I try being friendly no panel want to troll clumsy I might troll
Ellen I won't lie let me know I'll run with you if you want to run an LMFAO send the link link
link link link link link link I mean it's like it goes on for thousands of hours I mean every
night let him up let him tell his size he left he left oh did he I'll let him up right here
I dropped my phone. Are we reading messages? Or what are we doing?
Sorry about that. I didn't mean to.
You can read my messages. Go ahead and read my messages.
Go ahead and read them. Expose me.
All that's ever asked you is like, start a panel.
Or who's the number of the person that wants to start a panel?
That's all I've ever asked you, brother.
Or unless like, like the sincere shit.
Or I said like, twice, let's go to a panel.
Go, so did you like it?
Like, twice.
Go, so did you just-
So did we know each other?
Go, she asked for Bronzeberg to bring the panel for $100 to you?
I haven't gave anybody money unless I could send that shit with YouTube.
You would, you would, that Bronzeberg donated it to you, right?
For $100.
I don't, how can I get donations?
I don't have cash app.
I would send that shit if I had it.
You said, you gave Christina and Bronzeberg, you said, I'll get Psyche here if you'd pay
$100.
I went over there.
Never once happened.
Go ahead and prove that.
Think that is you guys let me raise your hand. You got some proof. No, I was just my bad
I thought yeah, my bad. I thought you're raising the hand
I never once said that and I put that on my mom's grave never once have I said that you don't remember
Never once I've never once offered money to make you join
Go ahead.
I'm going to ask you to Bronzeberg channel
and say we're going to split the money.
They're going to give us $100 bucks if you go over there.
And I go over there and then just laugh to us and talk.
I've got to get going.
Let me just say this.
Bye, Gotti.
Gotti's numerology network.
Next Monday at 8 o'clock.
Sike, thank you for everything.
You're the best.
You inspired me.
Without you, there would be no Gotti's numerology network
next week at 8 o'clock Monday.
Thank you so much.
Be good.
I'll see you later, Gotti.
Love you, Gotti.
He didn't say bye to ghosts, and that's upsetting.
Yeah, I never once said that and if I didn't say that that was a joke and you know that but I don't think I ever once said that
Why would I ever talk about money?
Why would I go over to Bronzeberg's panel to hang out with Christine unless I was uh-huh compensated are you actually being serious right now?
Yes, I told you that if you come over I'd give you $50
Do you know no I didn't say you would they would he said that that Bronzeberg and Christine would well
That's not me
But you broke with the deal you let us well let us assume that did happen and they said that and I told you that
How's that my fault? They didn't give you the money. That's not my fault. They promised to give you the money
Well, sue them because they broke the contract with you. Yeah, I'll sue them. That's fine. How's that my
Get out of here. Don't kick him. Come on. I mean, he's so annoying. I mean, I'll honestly I'll say you know
I knew that shit was gonna happen a little burden of proof and you run away now listen that never happened
You try to bring up text messages, which never happened
I did ask you because you are my what thought you're my friend obviously. I don't think anymore. So you're my
If I'm not your friend anymore, then you know, I don't know no reason to be in my show, right?
I don't like my friends. I don't like to talk my friends in the show
I don't like to talk to people that they badmouth me and when I put fucking spend time putting them in a video as a
Tribute, you know get all mad and accuse me and it's not even like your face
It's a cartoon version of like, I mean it looks even better than you. I mean, it's like what's your problem?
I mean Jesus
Age Christ bitch. I mean, it's like ghost and I'm not even complaining about money because I
Way past the time you started you stopped giving me money
I would still do whatever you asked me to do and stuff. I would go to any chat
You asked me to I would go defend you I would do all this shit
I didn't ask you for anything one time. I did ask you for something and you're like, oh, I don't know how to do that
I don't know how to do that and it's like
Okay, well fuck it then it's like but then you keep asking asking asking do this do this
Can you give me this woman's number? Oh, please hook me up
Please please I mean it's like question after question goes and I keep doing things for you
I think you don't need to choose super chats or something like that for two dollars each
Did he really ask you for a woman's number? Well, because they keep blocking him
Karen and Jimena, remember Jimena?
He called him in a like a he said if she was a transgender and then he like started bar bothering
I annexed the middle of the night and he said her link
Oh, go to this chat meet me there
She'd end up at betas or or some other chat like with all these trolls and he wouldn't be there
She'd be alone and she'd be like, why am I here?
You line up your asshole dude stop lying, bro
If we're gonna have this conversation stop kicking me unless it's actually talk about it
You actually want to I don't even want to talk about it, but we can
I'm kicking me though. You're gonna have to actually let me defend myself
That's like you making like a hit out on me like this kick them out. I just thought
I'm gonna get you know, that's not that's uh
I think I'm Zion X and why ask for a couple and it was cuz we were gonna start a panel and then I asked for you
Thank but no one has your number I guess but to start a panel
Because you went live remember last time I was on there when you went live. Yeah, dude. Don't you have Instagram?
No, I do not well. Just make one. We don't have Facebook or anything
So just make an Instagram account this way. I mean I could I don't have it though
I mean that's a good idea, but I don't have it though
I mean that's a good point, but I don't have it if someone needs to get a hold of me
They can get a hold of me through Instagram. I don't what I don't understand
It's like hey, so news now. I'm not saying some of them saying start a panel. I don't know what the fucking big deal is
If I texted you thing right now if I had your number I said hey start a panel. Do you think that would be a big?
Barber I want to watch prices, right? I'll be a contestant start a show prices, right getting your tuxedo fucking
You know rent the studio turn the lights get on saying I look like Bob Parker gonna be in the studio, right Bob
Barker just wake up and do it. I'm not gonna nothing
I'm not gonna give you anything or like, you know, I'm donating or anything, but I just want you to do something for me, right?
You know why that's a bad argument you have an open panel everybody comes up here and doesn't give you enough get out of here
I don't know panel. It's my decision who comes on the panel
It's called it's called a my panel my discretion not open. It's not like everyone can't come in here
It's up to me. Okay. It says open panel. It means there's a there's a there's a maybe unlocked door
But there's a big fucking buff
Black guy outside better to pick your ass
the
So chat, it's just us. How y'all doing?
Hopefully you're all saying good. That doesn't sound good when you talk about yourself, though.
Canadian fuck. I don't even understand what the argument was. I had a good argument earlier, but at this point
I don't even know what we're talking about. I don't know what you're arguing about specifically. No, I thought you were going to put your range in this.
I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I thought I
We're not trying to get you not gotcha moment shit. I do that plenty of time every day on YouTube
I don't need to do it on this panel. Actually. This is one of the cycle spin is one of the panels
I come to actually just fucking like hang out troll and take it. Yeah, that's good Chanel
What do you say? Sorry? I was talking to Chanel. I thought you were like on vacation or some shit
What do you mean? I came back. I came back on Sunday. Wow, they couldn't kept you for a couple more weeks. I wish
Did you have a good time?
Yeah, you joined the one time you're fucking out there drinking you're at like a pool or something
Yeah, I joined uh, yeah, I think is that when you started your own panel was that on vacation? No
No, the panel I did was like three four weeks ago now already
It was kind of fun though. I won't lie that shit was kind of cool. I'll do it again sometime
I just don't you should do it. You should do it more
Okay, well, you should wait like I texted psyche
I was like dude like starter panel like everyone else just end it like and there's so many people that want to go to a panel
That's when you should do it because you stay up later, too
So when everyone ends their stuff then start your own and then obviously you'll get more people
Yeah, they're looking for places to go, you know, but there's not I don't want everybody on my panel though
I'm very well. No not on your panel. Obviously you got to regulate that. No, but I mean I I'm
I'm very exclusive idea. It's not like just anybody can come up
I'm snobby, let's put it that way. Dobby is a free elf
Okay, so if so I come back up you're gonna keep fighting or is this over?
There was never a fight to begin with there was never a fight everything
I say I already know that like I don't want to be like I did kid
Are you asking me if I'm gonna win yes, but you asked me do I want to argue with them? No, obviously my friend well
I don't even know about anymore. He's probably
I don't do these good dick it for me like I don't know
You know you'll be fine. You let me on this panel, but I don't want our guy. Do I not think that is let me ask you question
Do I not every time I'm on a panel they talk shit about psyche. What do I do?
Do I ever join in driver? Am I not dirty fit inside?
Exactly. Oh, thanks kitten. No, I
and
You don't have to come back up brother. I I was so like
Man, that's feces though. That's female shit now logically. Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna defend myself
And you think that as if you were getting attacked you just send yourself to
How are you being attacked? That's what I want to know talking about the money shit
Like how dare you like all one person let us assume one person paid more than me that takes away everything I gave
Like what does that even mean also? I don't have a power don't have cash
I don't have any of that, but but didn't you ask him?
Who was he's like what he made the accusation I gave money or was it
Fucking know you gave them to know I didn't he doesn't show that on his panel. You would never know
I don't have that shit. I never did it. They paid by the way thing
I think you've been there they paid to kick me off and I
I told them to show the proof like who paid to kick me you just do that. He don't want to hear me talk
and money doesn't really they've never showed you paid they've literally never showed you yeah
That's money money doesn't say who the donor is either so unless you said it yourself in chat or from panel
So how can you two gonna be in me then if there's no way of proving it? How is that me? I know that's what I'm saying
Yeah, you try to go you try to talk to him, but you fucking this left and kick me out then
Don't know man. He's not a good debater, and I know he's not a good debater. I'm gonna go ahead and in my screen recorder
But I know he's not a good debater. I never once accused him of being that but
Don't come back. Why are you coming at me for I'm your only friend? Well, not your only friend
I want to be rude, but I'm one of your better friends on YouTube brother
I mean these YouTube streets. We don't have friends up here, and I'm one of your good friends
I'm sorry already kidding. I vote I sub to you weeks ago
Just in case you ever made a community post. I know you don't
I have not, but kitten seemed pretty cool. She's like, Hey, go up there. Well, I don't know if she's a chief and she's like, go up there and defend yourself, like let them let him join and she's pretty cool in the chat from what I know.
Yeah.
Yeah, she seemed pretty cool.
Yeah, I didn't mean to come at you. I didn't mean to come at you either like why do you seem to sleep?
Well, I was just angry earlier in my bed. I didn't mean to take it out. Yeah, I know it didn't bother me
I thought it was dumb. I mean for you to blame me for what a dumb ass, you know what?
This is not even entertaining. It was the dumb ass argument
It's like all these arguments have been happening between me and suck tonight dumb ass arguments. We can handle this one phone call
literally
Don't make a brought up receipts though, brother. We can bring up receipts. I would never do that
I would never actually do it. I know I threatened to do it
But I'd actually never do it like why would I bring up personal conversations, bro? You didn't to me though I
Told some bitch. What's her number? I want to start an open panel. What's wrong with that dude? It's not like I'm saying
Hey, show me your titties
No
I'm already accused of being a dog fucker. I don't need I don't need that on my plate here
You little Canadian fuck. Okay, psych come back up. I think we we've got resolution here
No, thank you
Yeah, yes, you we do come on. Let's drop it psych you drop it too
And we're gonna go forward. Yeah, but the thing about this imagine if it was like a personal phone call between us three and we handled it
This shit is live. I'm recording it. You're recording. It's all being this shit is live
He's in a post on a YouTube channel. Everyone can see this shit if I don't even myself. How do I look?
I'm gonna look like a dog fucker a great
Grape is I'm gonna look like a fucking a rubber bald head. Just kidding. But I look like you
Why did he kick you when you first came up here?
Cuz he doesn't like conflict. He likes it like to talk shit. You and he doesn't like
Okay, yeah, he came to me first though. Now he came in first. Oh, so then what do you mean?
He attacked you you attacked if I ever came at psyche first
No, he attacked me first you show my picture stuff and I say like that shit
Well, but then you put that new song up there and then you want to talk about money
Of all things man. Why would that picture thing bother you?
He would let somebody up here like 300 glow dip $0 and let somebody up me like up here
They take over well over $1,000 and then complain. I don't give any money that kind of hurt like motherfucker
What if what if I was out of work and didn't have money to send you ever think about that?
Maybe I just have the money to send all of you. Why would the picture? I do have the money to send
I just don't have cash up and I'm not getting it. I've been on that shit for like 33
I'm not getting that shit. Why would the picture?
Because it's disrespectful and he didn't end up just went for way last night. We didn't take that shit back
It's not there was nothing disrespectful in that
No, they were trying to be rude and I was like, oh, no, he's he's kind of cute
I was the woman not I was in the queen
But like oh, yeah, he's kind of cute one day for but they put that fucking me up there in that blue sweatshirt
And even a new one like
Making me look fat. I mean if you're gonna make me look fat at least make me look like Jabba the hut
Why make me look skinny?
I
Don't know that was a joke. That was joking didn't land. Sorry about that. Sorry about that
But no happened. I would never do that to you or him or I wouldn't even do it to my worst enemy
I would never do that
Okay, guys, I come up here. What up sir like it was this law for just coming in with like negative energy all night
And I'm putting down my video which I tried to like
That would be cute for you and okay. Yeah, fuck you. Okay. I'm ending this show having a night thing that is
All right later. Bye. Okay. I'll play one more song on the way out. I
Don't know it's like I mean I love thing that is I love on ghosts and it's like but it's like, you know what it's like
I mean, it's nothing to do with either. I mean, it's like really it's just like I don't know. I don't know
I'm so disrespected and stuff. I just try to like make everyone happy like I guess when you try many people happy sometimes
You make no one happy, right?
But I hope I do make you happy with this song and thanks for being here tonight. Hope you have fun. Thank you kidding cakes. I appreciate you
You're great
And I'm a unify, I'm a unify, I feel no soul unify
In the last little bus, you're just having a laugh
Till I'm past my bed, hey you guys, I don't want so much life
I could get you a little one or two ways
What's it gonna be, what's it gonna be
I said I felt like the whole world was begging me
To mean fire, but it's still for me, it's still for me
What's up?
Stop on me.